question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan 'We hire mercenaries and get in fights'.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In the Half-Life series,H.E.V stands for Hazardous Evasiveness Vest.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Pokemon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Pokmon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The ghosts in Pac-Man and Ms.Pac-Man have completely different behavior.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Resident Evil 7 is the first first-person Resident Evil game.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
